okay so Friday had a lesson
and I tried to install that thing
but it didn't work um
so I'm gonna put a clip
here of how that lesson went or what the
what the camera shot was like
it was uh way
way over exposed
uh the light
coming out the windscreen was literally like this
you can't see anything on the road
so there's no point it
being behind
so I was trying to basically see us
and see the road in front um
but you could basically just see us
and everything else out
the windshield was just a bright light
it was a sunny day
but I feel like there's more to do with my camera
you know uh
exposure and something to do some settings on the GoPro
and also where it was pointing was like mainly at us
rather than like focusing on the outside
try and find a good position for the GoPro
so I'm kind of thinking right here
looking at the driver
this might be a good place but uh
you can see that if I edit it this
this is what it looks like so
here so I'm thinking it gets the driver
the learner
maybe a bit of me but that's not really that important
now I need to get the double sticky tape thing
stick it on and hopefully we have a winner this angle
okay another dilemma is we've got this angle
what I found from here is that this is a bit like
supposed to be sticky here
so I feel like the weight pulls on this maybe
and it might fall off
there's less weight going down on it maybe
there's a bit more grip
but is that
I don't know
it's a weird angle I don't know
I feel like I kinda like this
and that sees the whole driver's experience
what they see high height as well
let's go I wanna do both
oh no I can't um
here try without the super wide
*squeal in terror*
how that
I've committed squeeze
no
I've lost all the stick
huh right how do I stick that on there duct tape
hold on
oh rubbish whole thing waste of time
how did I get it on there
okay have an idea
I've got a head
that might work
okay new idea
head strap
that is actually decent
so that's basically exactly where I wanted it
now that is something else
bit shaky might be decent
how did that sound
so find out in the footage afterwards
alright let's go for a drive
so I thought this is more IGTV
don't know what that is
until just then I thought everything was real
but now thinking about it
I have seen an app called IGTV
which I think is for watching longer videos
so maybe this is where this will be
so yeah
alright so we're chopping and changing in between
little bits of light
which is good
I'm actually so excited to see how this goes over bumps
that's probably gonna shake a bit
alright let's see how it goes